Solyom Nagy-Györkös

Information Security Analyst

+36 30 332 1178

nagydsolyom@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/solyomnagygyorkos/

Budapest, Hungary (relocation possible)



Versatile and results-oriented Information Security Analyst with a unique blend of technical expertise in risk assessment, security monitoring, and cloud security, combined with 10+ years of experience in cross-cultural collaboration and customer support. Successfully delivered a managed security service project for PaaS solutions, showcasing my ability to adapt to diverse environments and deliver impactful solutions. Seeking a challenging role where I can leverage my diverse skill set and "can-do" attitude to enhance security posture.

Achievements

Anonymous DDoS Incident Responder: Executing a successful incident response, limiting a large-scale DDoS attack within 8 hours, significantly outperforming industry averages of 2–3 days Managed Security Service: spearheading the implementation and delivery of a managed security service offering projected to generate \$1.8 million in annual profit.

Community Development: blogging for knowledge sharing and evolving write-up capabilities successfully generated 1600 organic reaches in 1 year

 ${\it Automatization:} \ \ {\it automated} \ \ {\it CTI} \ \ information \ \ resource \ \ aggregation \ \ from \ \ image \ \ files, \ reducing \ \ resolution \ time \ with 90\% \ and \ backlog \ with 87.5\%$

IAM and Security Controls: managing the implementation of passkey based MFA locally and globally, respectively, ~ 100 employees in 1 month and ~ 1000 employees in 3 months

Bug Hunting: identified, isolated, and reported issue EDR solution, causing critical malfunction for JVM applications for 2 weeks

Certifications

Certifications	
• CompTIA Network+ N10-009	learning
• CompTIA Security+ SY0-701	learning
Pluralsight Python 3 Fundamentals	learning
TryHackMe Advent of Cyber 2024 (THM-WTEXDIVIJ1)	12.2024
Security Blue Team Junior Analyst (920901949)	12.2024
 Google Cloud Partner Skill Badge Challenge (skill_badge_star_digital_sticker_ADL8VBOR) 	11.2024
 SOCRadar Fundamental Threat Intelligence Training (66571dee7d5c99de1d0aaade) 	05.2024
 Google Professional Cloud Security Engineer (3928a009709e457cac74118bb577ddcf) 	02.2024
TryHackMe Advent of Cyber 2023 (THM-FPRSNLB0LU)	12.2023
Liferay pre-SOC Training	12.2023
 Lets Defend SOC Analyst Learning Path (37005162-5614-41bb-a555-2447c79281e6) 	11.2023
Antisyphon Training:	
 Getting Started in Security with BHIS and MITRE ATT&CK 	09.2023
 MITRE ATT&CK Framework and Tools (b01c07ea-8cee-4f8f-aedb-ec5bcffc1f94) 	08.2023
 SOC Core Skills (d5c8beaaf8124663b7cbe78f5ea62a78) 	06.2023
 Active Defense & Cyber Deception (afeac8ae-0695-437c-a36f-fce297e2416d) 	05.2023
• CompTIA Security+ SY0-601	05.2023
Active Countermeasures Cyber Threat Hunting Training	04.2023
(D77e72a87da02ba1c40F7cb8deADaD11f949431d)	

Professional Experience

Liferay Hungary Kft

2024 - present

Information Security SOC Analyst

- Proactively monitoring, analyzing, and responding to security incidents across diverse platforms, ensuring efficient threat mitigation and vulnerability remediation.
- Assessing and prioritizing security threats and vulnerabilities, enabling rapid mitigation and improved organizational security posture.
- Supporting the development, implementation, and maintenance of security strategies, infrastructure, and awareness initiatives.
- Collaborating effectively with diverse stakeholders, providing expertise and facilitating communication to enhance security awareness and incident response.
- Enhancing team capabilities in the last 6 months by mentoring 6+ colleagues, facilitating knowledge transfer of critical tools and processes, resulting in improved workload distribution and increased project capacity.
- Delivering impactful presentations, fostering open communication and increasing the security team's accessibility across the company by 300%.

Liferay Hungary Kft

2021 - 2024

Customer Support Engineer

- Provided L2 support for enterprise customers using Liferay DXP and Liferay Experience Cloud.
- Configured Java web-based test environments with MySQL databases and Tomcat application servers.
- Investigated and reproduced reported issues, collaborating with technical engineers for resolutions.
- Monitored the bug-fixing process and facilitated knowledge sharing through documentation and training.

Contractor 2011 – 2021

Professional Dancer

- Mastered various dance styles and choreographies, performing professional shows.
- Developed strong situational improvisation skills and the ability to quickly adapt to new routines.
- Demonstrated ability to collaborate effectively with international teams and stakeholders, navigating diverse cultural landscapes.

Skills and Technologies

SentinelOne XDR, SOCRadar CTIP, GCP environment, Cloud Armor WAF, Palo Alto Prisma CSPM, Exabeam SIEM, Threat Intelligence, Security Incident Response, Threat Hunting, Security Audits, Compliance, Zendesk, Jira, Confluence, Public Speaking

Languages

Hungarian: Native

English: Proficient C1 (written and spoken)

2010 - present

German: Elementary level (written and spoken) - learning

Community Engagement

ISC2, TryHackMe, Google Cloud Community, Threat Hunter Community, Simply Cyber, Antisyphon Training, Black Hills Information Security, LetsDefend, Liferay

Education

Software Developer Soter-Line Oktatási Központ 2020-2022